Now, how to remove cats from sorted at a given assorted array a are as follows.
Remove the duplicates from this sorted array.
We have this is the array.
OK, and we have the at 40 and 40.
How to remove this, these duplicates.
The algorithm?
And the way of removing this double tickets is by.
Identifying I and I plus one and start comparing the elements, so it checks the first element and the
second element.
The second and the third.
And so until it reached that duplicate, so.
If I equal I +1, then stop.
There is a double act in this way, we are going to make the removed public algorithms and see how to
implement it in the code.
So if I equal I +1, then the LANG- I make and then a variable called Len and it is zero since it reverses
and I duplicate 40 and 40, it change to one.
So we have one public and then I and I +1 continue to the rest of the array when it sees through double
tickets like I equal I +1 increase len variable by one.
So if we have five double tickets, it will have Len equal to five.
OK, now we will remove the duplicate.
And remove that.
And this is switch the element back and remove the empty space.
How to implement this and code.
Let's see.
We start by making and a method called removed.
It contains or took in the perimeter entry and into and we start by comparing if an equal equal to zero
or an equal equal to one return.
And so if we are comparing or removing cats of the sort sorted array and an equal equal to one, we
can't find them.
OK.
So create a variable called end len.
It's of type and and name LEN and create an index equal to zero or entire.
We start by a for loop.
This is the array array and.
And this is that these are the elements.
We start from index zero.
Tell I less than and minus one because we are going to continue to compare the elements at index and
minus one.
If they're array at index, I is not equal array at index I +1 then continue.
OK, so it starts by comparing.
It found a duplicate effort and forth, so array of land plus plus equal array at index high.
So it found array of Lynn Plus plus equal array at and minus one and a return len.
How thus means it will increase LEN by one and remove the element at index.
That we have found that there are duplicate.
Plus one where removed and this is we switch back array at land plus plus equal array and minus one.
And then we remove it and return.